[tense, rhythmic music playing]
I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE EVERYTHING.
BUT I CAN'T.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
[lighter clicks]
[tense music building]
[flesh sizzles]
[officer, echoing] Rocío Owono Durán.
You can go.
[tense music continues]
[tense music fades]
Rocío's all right. They let her go.
Why don't you have clothes on?
Dude, if you don't come out,
my dad'll be pissed.
He can go fuck himself.
What's that smell? What did you do?
- Eric, what did you do?
- Get outta here!
[birds singing]
[Alfonso] Where's your cousin?
Okay, yeah. I've had enough.
Dad, he's not feeling well.
Let him stay home just this once.
Relax. It's not a big deal.
When he's like this, we leave him alone.
María, he can't just do whatever he wants.
That's not how this works.
Good morning, family.
Good morning, honey.
How are you? You all right?
Yeah, Auntie. I'm great. Why?
- [Eric singing]
- [engine starts]
[Nico sniffles]
[speaking inaudibly]
[Virginia on PA] Good morning.
ARE YOU COMING TO SCHOOL?
[Virginia] And welcome to the first
Pan-African Gathering for Excellence.
[Eric] Hey, Chloe!
[Virginia] As part
of the Excellentia Academic Global League,
today Las Encinas is proud
to present its exchange scholarships
with the two best private schools
on the African continent.
The Lua Jean school in Maputo, Mozambique,
and Parkhurst College
in Cape Town, South Africa.
Thanks to the initiative
of the Catalina Durán
Hispanic-Pan-African Foundation.
I can't keep pulling strings
to get you out
of this sort of situation, Rocío.
I'm sorry, Mom.
The pressure on women
that look like us is triple.
You can't change things through squatting.
Whereas as a judge, I can do something.
[sighs]
Take advantage of the education
we're giving you
to try and learn
to change things in an intelligent way.
And a civilized one.
Your gear for the match and your dress
for the gala are in the trunk.
Get them and go inside.
C'mon. Let me skip school.
I'm exhausted. I need a shower.
You can shower and change at school.
[Rocío sighs]
I've been organizing this
with Virginia for a while.
[Rocío sighs]
[trunk opens]
[indistinct chatter]
What's up?
Morning.
I keep texting, and no response.
Am I smothering you?
[sighs] Look, Iván, you said
you'd be fine with just friendship.
So we can be friends and also classmates.
But ultimately,
we've got our own lives to live.
Did you talk to Omar?
[sighs] See you in class.
Guys, this is Fikile.
She's a student from Parkhurst.
Um, Cape Town.
- Hi. How are you?
- Hi.
[Virginia] So you guys
can talk a bit about the exchange.
Okay? Have a seat. Have fun.
- Nice to meet you guys.
- [both] Nice to meet you.
Uh, and you can call me Fiks.
Okay.
Are any of you guys
gonna apply for the exchange?
- I don't think so.
- Mm. Not for now, no.
Ah, okay.
[crowd cheers and applauds]
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [crowd whistles]
Holy shit!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Just come down here.
- Why?
- I got something to show you.
Yeah, I'm good.
[clicks tongue] You're goddamn annoying.
Come down. Pretty please.
Now what?
["Alala" by CSS playing on speaker]
[Eric] It's on our playlist.
Don't you ever get tired of
degrading yourself to get some attention?
[laughs] You make sex tapes. You tell me.
[quietly] Wow.
♪ A-la-la, a-la-la… ♪
Sorry. I'm just trying to be cool
with you, but you keep locking me out.
Yeah. Well, I never asked you to.
♪ A-la-la, a-la-la ♪
♪ Gimme more too ♪
♪ I wanna be in that crazy band ♪
- ♪ Or meu cu, a-la-la, a-la-la ♪
- [singing inaudibly]
♪ Would you be kind? ♪
♪ Gimme one, little more ♪
- ♪ And I'll be super fine ♪
- [Chloe laughs]
♪ A-la-la, a-la-la ♪
♪ You're so cool… ♪
- [song stops]
- For real? That's awful.
They arrested me, and he did nothing.
- He confuses me.
- [sighs]
After that and walking in on me,
he came home, head covered in blood.
And this morning,
he was impossible to deal with.
Five minutes later,
he's singing like nothing was wrong.
You know one
of his tattoos is a semicolon, right?
I don't know. He has so many bruises,
it's hard to tell what's what.
- Why?
- [Eric] Go, Rocío! Let's go!
Was that him just now?
Rocío! Rocío!
Listen, dude.
I'm gonna have to keep him
at arm's length.
- I hope you understand.
- No, yeah. I do. I get it.
[Eric chanting] Rocío! Rocío!
- Are they asking for help or something?
- No, he's excited.
- [whistle blows]
- [Eric] Let's go, team!
[crowd cheering]
[ominous music playing]
Over here! Pass!
[ominous music building]
- [background sounds fade]
- [Iván panting, echoing]
- [crowd cheering, muffled]
- [horn blares, echoes]
- [Iván gasping]
- [music intensifies]
[horn blares]
[distorted sounds echoing]
[crowd cheers]
[ref blows whistle]
Hey. Hey.
Why don't we get out of here? Yeah?
- [Isa] Are you okay?
- [quietly] Yeah. Yeah.
[Isa] Are you sure?
I'm fine. Thanks.
[Fiks] Come on.
Let's go.
[music grows somber]
[crowd continues cheering]
[music fades]
I never imagined that a casual match
would have that effect.
You must've had an inkling.
Otherwise, you would've played.
- Right?
- [Fiks] Mm-hmm.
Why don't you apply for the exchange?
Go to South Africa.
That way, you can get a break, you know?
Time and distance
really are the best medicine.
[tense music pulsing]
How do I apply for this exchange?
I'll show you.
[tense music building]
[cell phone chimes]
- [clicks tongue]
- [cell phone clatters]
[sighs]
[computer chimes]
I THOUGHT I COULD HANDLE EVERYTHING.
BUT I CAN'T.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
- [tense music swells]
- [thunder crashes]
[Omar breathing shakily]
[ominous music playing]
[sirens wailing]
[ominous music intensifies]
[music fades]
TALK REPORTS
[Omar] 90% of people who kill themselves
show warning signs beforehand.
People think they're cries for attention.
And they're not. They're reaching out.
I'll pass your reports on
to the Psychology and Pedagogy Department.
And that's it?
They're the experts, Omar.
Whereas you just do the paperwork.
[Omar sighs, scoffs]
[speaking inaudibly]
[Luis] Was there anything else?
Yeah.
A list of students
getting scholarships for tuition.
That's confidential, and you know it.
[somber music playing]
[under breath] Son of a bitch.
Okay. I sent you the app login.
So you can read and reply
if you see anything out of the ordinary.
I can't handle this alone,
and that idiot Luis is useless.
Is that why you haven't responded?
You don't think you're capable?
And because I once said
those same words myself.
It's just too much for me.
How'd you pull yourself out?
[thunder rumbles]
[somber music playing]
[Omar breathing shakily]
[Joel] Omar?
Omar!
It's Joel from the association.
Do you remember me?
Get outta here.
Omar, please, don't do this.
Go away, please.
Omar, look at me.
[crying] No. I can't anymore.
No. I just can't.
Omar, please, look at me.
- [panting]
- [Omar] Please.
Don't do this.
Please, Omar.
- [Omar exhales]
- [Joel] That's it. There you go.
- That's better.
- [emotional piano music playing]
[emotional piano music building]
[Omar sobs]
[thunder rumbles]
[emotional music fading slowly]
IF YOU CAN'T DO IT ALONE,
I'M HERE TO HELP WITH WHATEVER YOU NEED.
I KEEP MISTREATING
PEOPLE WHO SHOW ME AFFECTION.
I FEEL LONELY, AND I'M TO BLAME.
That writing style rings a bell.
Wanna take over?
Do you think some people are evil?
I mean, born that way?
I think there are people in lots of pain.
SEMICOLON TATTOO
ANXIETY, DEPRESSION, SUICIDE ATTEMPT
[Eric] Hey. I'm so sorry
for leaving you in the lurch.
I'd blow me off too. I was a coward.
[sighs] Well, you've apologized now.
Thanks. See you.
[Eric] Please don't be mad at me.
- It's not like we're super close friends.
- Yeah, but we could be, though.
After that moment we shared
in the squat house, it was fuckin' great.
- Until it all went to shit.
- I gotta run. Sorry.
[Rocío sighs]
I know I'm a piece of shit
who disappoints everyone.
That's why I always end up alone!
[quietly] Eric, not right now.
What else could it be?
Fear? I scare you? Just tell me.
Tell me I scare you
and that you'd rather ghost me entirely.
'Cause I'm not worth it.
You don't get my actions,
and it's scaring you away.
Like my parents.
[somber music playing]
Or don't say anything.
So I can stop thinking
that you were ever worth it.
[somber music intensifies]
[muffled] Hey! Eric! Hey!
Eric, look at me. Breathe.
Breathe.
Come on, breathe.
That's it. You got this.
That's it. Calm down. I'm here.
[music fades slowly]
[knocking on door]
Luis!
[tense music playing]
[tense music building]
ACCOUNT HOLDER: IVÁN CRUZ CARVALHO
LEAVE THIS GROUP?
LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE
SARAUL.GOALS HAS HIGHLIGHTED A STORY.
[Raúl on phone]
Tonight, we've seen a lot of bling-bling,
but one more gem's gotta shine.
Sara…
will you be my wife?
[girl laughs]
[heart thumping]
- [background sounds fade]
- [heart beats faster, echoing]
- [beating stops]
- Baby, are you okay?
Yeah.
I mean, I think your boyfriend
was being a bit extra with that proposal,
to be honest.
We're too young to be putting
all of our eggs in one basket.
How's it going with Dídac?
Fine.
Yeah, it's going all right.
I'm still trying to forget about him,
but it's fine.
Anyway, nothing that a good party
can't cure, my darling.
Okay, guys!
Let's show our African friends
how we throw a good party here, right?
Oh no, honey.
It is us who have come to show you.
Oh, honey. We'll see.
Oh, yes, we will.
["Mama dey Party" by Bryte playing]
C'mon, party! Whoo!
Are you sure
people are not gonna hate us for this?
This is not cultural appropriation?
Girl, what? No.
We are the organizers, okay?
We gave you this dress code
because we want you to have
a full, immersive party experience.
Love it. You guys are in charge.
This is your home.
- You can do whatever you want.
- Thank you.
Whoo!
[girl cheers]
[song stops abruptly]
[keys jangling]
How is he?
He took the pill, calmed down,
and went to bed, but he was a wreck.
Coz! Why aren't you dressed yet?
- What are you talking about?
- They're all at the party.
Well, maybe you should stay home tonight.
[Eric] No. I'm in the mood to get turnt.
Plus, the African kids are here.
We gotta be good hosts.
Listen to your aunt.
- You got three minutes, Nico.
- I don't think you should go out.
- You're not coming? Then I'm out.
- [María] Eric.
- Later.
- Eric, dear. Wait a minute-
[door slams]
Nico. Nico, honey. Tag along.
Please keep an eye on him.
Shit, María.
He'll take Nico down with him.
Dad, don't worry about me.
I can handle it.
[woman] Can you think of a better idea?
Are you serious?
Tell me you're not serious right now.
You know who they remind me of?
- Who?
- My parents, when they're fighting.
I see. [chuckles]
My parents fight all the time too,
to be honest.
Do you think you and I will be like that
20 years from now?
Hysterical, frustrated, and loud?
I mean, I think that the worst snake oil
they try to sell us in life
is the urge to grow up.
Because when you do,
and life just knocks you down,
then you're like these two morons.
And then, all you want to do
is to be our age again and immature.
[Dídac chuckles softly]
Let's make the most of it
while we're young.
- [Isa] Mm-hmm.
- [cell phone chimes]
- What's up?
- I'm not sure.
- Ooh.
- What?
Something's up with the music.
That's weird.
- No.
- I gotta go.
- No. [sighs]
- Yeah, I gotta fix it. I'll see you later.
- Yeah, from afar.
- [man 1] For heaven's sake.
[woman] I'm leaving.
- Get away from me!
- [man 1] Jesus fucking Christ!
- [dramatic music plays on laptop]
- [door opens]
[man 2] I truly appreciate you meeting
with me again.
- [door closes]
- [man 2] Seriously, I'm telling you.
It's really wonderful,
the way that you've been working, Cata.
Thank you. Again, please forgive me
for rushing you so much.
[on headphones] With this eviction,
it would cause us to lose time.
Luena, don't leave yet.
[man 2] While they gain opportunities.
Don't you get it?
Huh? Huh?
There. Two hundred.
Feel free to count it, Catalina.
Take your time.
I trust you.
But this is the last favor, Martín.
- It's always the last one.
- [Catalina] No.
When I moved the social center's
eviction ahead, my daughter was arrested.
I'm not putting myself at risk anymore.
She says she moved the eviction up.
Find me judges named Catalina.
- We don't have a warrant for it, though.
- Well, he's bribing her, so fuck that.
[ominous music playing]
- Oh shit.
- What?
Her daughter goes to school
with Isadora and Dídac.
- [ "Sheesh" by Toya Delazy playing]
- ♪ Sheesh! ♪
- ♪ What's up? ♪
♪ What's up… ♪
- [phone beeps]
- Dídac, where are you?
You're taking absolutely forever.
Are you in my room? I'll be right there.
- [Catalina] I'm leaving.
- [phone chimes and vibrates]
[tense music playing]
[door opens]
I don't believe it.
Papá!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
- [Martín] Hello, my darling.
- Hello!
- [Martín] Wanted to surprise you.
- [Isa] How are you?
I just wanted to see the look of surprise
on your face.
[Isa] Oh, I missed you so much.
- Yeah. I'm so happy to be here.
- Hi, Isa.
- [Isa] Mm.
- I'm going.
- Talk later.
- Yeah.
- Sweetie, you are gorgeous.
- What was Rocío's mother doing here?
- Don't worry. I'll explain it in a bit.
- Talking about exchange scholarships.
Ultimately, we pay
a ton of money for them.
And us parents have to deal
with everything. It's not fair.
Mom, if I wanted to be lied to,
I would've asked you, but I asked Papá.
- See how she treats me? All the time.
- Can we please… Yeah.
Let's, uh, try to play nice
and have a drink. Us three.
- It'll be so nice after all this time.
- Come on, dear.
- [Isa] It's been too long.
- [Martín] Let's go.
- Let's go. Come on.
- [ "Sohaa Gb3k3" by Onipa playing]
Our social media engagement has grown
like gangbusters since the announcement.
Everyone, and I mean everyone,
is writing to us.
They're offering us megabucks
for wedding collaborations.
- Blown away, for real.
- [cell phone chimes]
SARA, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
AREN'T YOU COMING TO THE CLASSES?
Okay. Why's a teacher texting a student?
Just class stuff.
At night, though?
I THINK IT'S BEST IF I DON'T…
I mean, is she in love with you, or what?
- [scoffs]
- Huh? Is that it?
What are you talking about?
Here's to Sara and Raúl.
[Joel] What's good, guys?
- Hey. What's up?
- Look, here we are with Saraul. Goals.
Yeah! And also
with the African exchange students,
who've come to teach us a lesson
about the right way to throw a party.
- Here's to all you beautiful people.
- [laughs] Yep. Hello. See you later.
- [Joel] All together!
- [Dalmar] Have you seen this?
- [Joel] Come on.
- [Dalmar] He wants to be an influencer.
- He's in for a rude awakening.
- [Omar] What makes you say that?
[Joel] The drinks,
the lights, the music, everything…
Well, since he has
a few thousand followers,
he says that he can live off that
if he puts in the time.
- He'll quit working?
- [Dalmar] He better not.
I can't pay more for this apartment
'cause he wants to scratch his dick
and post stories.
["Sohaa Gb3k3" playing on phone]
[somber music playing]
["Sohaa Gb3k3" continues]
[Joel sighs]
[Joel] Iván!
I know I'm doing everything wrong.
[gentle music playing]
[Joel] And… [sighs]
And honestly, I…
I didn't want to hurt
either of you. [sighs]
In the end, I'm hurting both of you.
But the thing is…
the thing is, I need to do right by Omar.
Because I love him, and…
and I feel like…
I feel like I'm letting him down.
And we don't deserve this.
Not you, me, or him.
Work things out with him.
And tell him he's a lucky guy.
[gentle music swells]
["Gimme Any Riddim" by DJ Tess playing]
♪ Yo ♪
♪ You don't know ♪
♪ It's night upon this one, yeah… ♪
Here's to grand disappointments.
How 'bout grand discoveries? Cheers.
♪ DJ Tess and Nan Kolè, yeah… ♪
Wow.
- [sighs]
- If you like him, why do you ghost him?
I'm not ghosting.
Yeah, you are.
Well, I'm not a romantic like you.
And then you end up doing shots
with friends.
[chuckles] Wanna get our dance on?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
♪ Out the box and outside defined ♪
♪ Not in the flock
I will not change my mind ♪
♪ Cool me boss
'Cause I won't fall in line ♪
♪ I make my own line, I am pro
Got my own mind, I'm on my own grind ♪
♪ I don't fill a suit
I like my own clothes ♪
♪ Serious ♪
♪ Give me any rhythm, yeah ♪
♪ You don't know I kill 'em, mm-hmm ♪
♪ The beat's when I instant my move ♪
♪ Drop the foot, time gets another move
What'd I say? Yeah, give me any rhythm ♪
♪ I kill 'em, watch me ska to this set ♪
♪ Back to it, drop the soul ♪
♪ Right up your ears
While you listen, yeah ♪
- I wanted to tell you-
- [Chloe] What?
What're you looking at?
At you.
At me?
Maybe stop looking at me and kiss me.
["Polo Munene" by KOKOKO! playing]
[both breathing heavily and kissing]
[breathily] So? Do you like it? Huh?
Just what I needed.
Oh, really?
[Eric] Mm.
You mean the shot or me?
You, for sure.
[both panting]
[Eric inhales sharply]
[Fiks] Hey.
- I have to go.
- You're leaving?
Yeah, I have
a super early flight tomorrow, so…
It was a pleasure.
It really was.
I'll see you in Cape Town, yeah?
- See you there.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be great.
- Great.
- Bye.
[panting]
- Mm.
- What was it you needed again?
I don't need someone
to remind me I'm a garbage human.
Just someone who's fucked up too.
And hates herself as much as I do.
- [panting]
- You're such a piece of shit.
[Eric] Hey!
[sighs, whispers] Fuck.
Dumbass!
[slams loudly]
I think I'll have a gin.
- Thanks.
- [ "Good One Deh" by Bryte playing]
[Iván] Chloe?
Chloe! What's wrong?
- Leave me alone, please.
- What did he do?
- He didn't do anything.
- What's the matter?
[crying softly]
- ♪ I said ♪
- ♪ Okay ♪
- ♪ Good one deh ♪
- ♪ One deh ♪
- [song fades]
- [gentle music playing]
[excited chatter in distance]
LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE
NEW MESSAGE
[footsteps approaching]
[Sara] Wanna head out?
Uh, sure. Here.
[somber music playing]
Hey, Sara?
Am I a monster?
Why are you asking that?
I know I have a lot of room to grow,
but I only tried to love you
and be protective.
Well, yeah. I know.
Do you really?
I do.
What's this about?
Forget it.
[exhales shakily]
Thanks for letting me vent.
If you need anything, you know I'm here.
Yeah. I appreciate it.
Chloe!
Oh, my mother. I gotta go.
Thank you.
- Take care.
- [Chloe sniffles]
Sweetheart,
aren't you freezing your butt off?
- [music fades]
- [car door opens]
[car door closes]
- [Carmen] What's up with your eyes?
- Nothing.
Don't tell me it's nothing.
You're like a sad puppy dog.
What's the matter?
Why were you hugging Iván, crying?
Honey, I hope
you weren't thinking about trying-
Fuck. Ew, Mom. Of course not.
I mean, Iván's awesome.
He just listened to me
and supported me when I needed it.
It's so nice to hear
you say that, darling.
That's what I want,
you two bonding and connecting.
Mom, can you maybe stop thinking
about your fucking plan
and think about me?
What plan? What are you saying?
[cell phone chimes]
PEOPLE CARE BECAUSE THEY KNOW THAT,
DEEP DOWN,
YOU HAVE A DAMAGED HEART THAT IS WORTH IT.
FIND IT AND NURTURE IT.
[cell phone chimes]
Hey, Chloe.
Chloe, c'mon, now.
Chloe, talk to me.
He wants to do the exchange program.
So he can get a fresh start.
[Carmen] Where to?
South Africa.
- Where?
- Yes. And we're gonna leave him alone.
'Cause what he needs is time
and space to find himself again.
Not to have a dopey mother show up.
Much less me as a sister.
["Chamegei" by Thornato playing]
- [Carmen] Fasten your seat belt.
- [belt clicks]
[car engine starts]
[rhythmic dance music continues]
[speaking inaudibly]
You seen my cousin anywhere?
I'm really worried about him.
- [Roberta] Exactly.
- You know, to give each other-
It's nice that all three of us
are together as a family.
Yeah. It'd be nice
if it didn't happen once in a blue moon.
- No more excuses.
- [Isa] Hmm.
What did I say earlier?
- But do you promise?
- See? Look. [kisses]
- [Roberta] Like when she was little.
- Hon, I promise.
You'll be seeing me a lot more frequently.
- I better.
- [Martín] Of course you will, my love.
[Martín] Mm. Hm.
I missed you.
Okay. I have something I have to handle,
but I'll be back.
[Roberta] Where are you going?
- Can't you stay longer? She's nonstop.
- [Martín] Just for a sec.
- [Roberta] She's nonstop.
- Hurry back.
- Do not badmouth my father.
- You're not hearing what I said.
- I'm listening.
- I saw it. It's not like I heard about it.
- Have you seen Eric?
- [both] No.
Oh! Tell her. Go on.
That her mom's corrupt
and doing business with my father.
- We can pull the wool off all our eyes.
- She what now?
Never mind. We haven't seen Eric.
I don't know where he is.
- What'd you say about my mother?
- Nothing, Rocío. Forget it.
- I'm kinda in the middle of an argument.
- But why'd you bring up my mother?
Get over it, Rocío. I didn't mean it.
Can I have an argument in peace?
- All right, look. I don't-
- [Isa] No.
- Why don't you believe my own eyes?
- Dídac, I'm begging you.
Don't say anything.
You're driving me up the wall.
["Traaa" by CRRDR playing]
What you want?
[rhythmic music thumping on speakers]
[phone chimes, vibrates]
INCOMING CALL: MOM
- [Eric] Let me go! Bastard!
- [man] Calm down.
- [Eric] Son of a bitch!
- What's going on?
[grunts] Let me go!
He was throwing himself
against the windows.
We restrained him
to keep him from cracking his head open.
Jesus, Eric!
Fuck off, all right?
I don't understand
why you'd rather beat yourself up
than ask us for help.
You're the one pushing us away.
Eric.
[Rocío] Nico, I've gotta go.
[Eric sighs]
So do you think it's my fault
that those I care about abandon me?
Yeah, no fucking way.
We'll see how long you last.
[Nico chuckles]
[dance music building]
[inhales]
[snorting]
On the bright side,
now we can be a family.
Come on. Together.
You need to give her a break.
Can you fix yourself up? Thank you.
She'll make mistakes here and there.
But she's always wanted
what was best for you.
What's the matter?
You all right?
Are you bribing Rocío's mother?
- [music stops]
- [clamoring]
- [officer 1] Nobody move!
- [guests screaming]
Police! This is a raid!
[officer 1] We ask for your cooperation!
[officer 2] Move!
[officer 3] Get over there.
I need you to stay over there!
[tense music playing]
[officer 4] Come on.
[crowd clamoring]
[sirens wailing]
[music grows somber]
[thunder rumbles in distance]
[engine starts]
[indistinct shouting]
[thunder crackles]
[thunder crashes]
[thunder continues rumbling outside]
[gentle music playing]
[sighs]
- [Joel] Fuck.
- [keys clatter]
Come here.
Surprise. [chuckles]
I know. It got a bit wet.
[music fades]
You're very quiet.
Is it true you got a scholarship?
[sighs] No.
Well, all right.
Okay, then, how are you paying for school?
Someone offered to pay.
[Omar] Someone?
Who? In return for?
For nothing.
You answered the second part
but not the first.
[scoffs] That doesn't matter.
[Omar] I know it's Iván.
Anything else?
That's all there is.
I think there's more.
- Are you in love with him?
- [gentle music playing]
[Joel sighs]
I'm not sure.
But I don't want to leave you.
Why?
You scared for me?
You'll stay in something
that makes you unhappy?
I'm not unhappy with you.
Joel.
We both know
you've checked out of this relationship.
- Be with him.
- What?
- I couldn't. No.
- Joel, honey. I mean it. Go there.
[crying] No, Omar.
I can't do this to you. I won't.
- But it's what you want.
- No, I don't. I'm in love with you.
And I love you,
but don't stay out of a sense of debt.
I'm in your debt, really.
There's nothing to repay.
Great. Neither of us owes anything.
There's no debt, just love.
And my love won't let me be the bastard
who keeps you from living out your life.
[Joel sighs]
Be with him.
Go, and I'll clean this up.
[gentle music fades]
- [thunder rumbling]
- [Chloe] Hmm.
[ominous music playing]
Goddammit, Mom.
[Chloe] Mom.
[quietly] The fuck are you doing?
Just talking to Iván. He cannot go
to the other side of the world.
Okay. Aren't you his mother?
Think what's best for him.
He doesn't need you, Mom.
He doesn't need us. Not now.
Okay?
- Please, I said no.
- [doorbell rings]
[quietly] Jesus Christ.
- Hi.
- [Carmen] Hi, sweetheart.
I came to thank you
for how nicely you treated Chloe.
No worries. She needed a friend.
See? You're such an angel. Can we come in?
I'd also like to talk to you
about something important.
- [Iván] Is something the matter?
- No.
Can I tell you in there?
Sure, come in.
Coming or not?
- Hello.
- [Chloe] Hello.
Why are you here?
Well, I came to see you,
but… but I can leave if you're busy.
No, you're good. I swear.
You can come in
'cause we were just leaving.
Mom, you and I are going home.
Hey, are you all right?
[Joel sighs]
So you know, for me, it was also
one of the best nights in a long time.
[both chuckle]
Now, let's go.
Iván deserves a good time, okay?
I'm going to tell him, Chloe.
Okay. But how 'bout another day,
all right?
["Suddenly" by Anna Calvi playing]
[both panting]
♪ Crawling out ♪
♪ You need to protect me ♪
♪ I'm calling out ♪
♪ Find me a stronger hand ♪
♪ I stand on the edge ♪
♪ Of silence ♪
- ♪ Better confess ♪
- [Joel sighs]
♪ It tastes like I'm leavin' ♪
♪ Suddenly, I'll leave it all behind ♪
- ♪ Tell your heart to jump to another ♪
- [Iván panting]
♪ But darkness grows ♪
♪ And, oh, a never- ending night ♪
♪ I stand on the edge ♪
♪ Of silence ♪
♪ Better confess ♪
♪ It tastes like I'm leavin' ♪
♪ Suddenly, I'll leave it all behind ♪
[rain pattering]
[keys jangle]
♪ Ashes to ashes ♪
♪ It leaves me with nothin' ♪
♪ I'm fallin' away ♪
♪ Well, if you want it… ♪
Omar? Omar?
Omar!
Omar…
Oh God. Omar!
♪ Suddenly, I'll leave it all behind ♪
["Suddenly" continues]
["Suddenly" ends]
[somber instrumental music playing]